THE WAY AND JUST SEE IT IN THEIR
EYES, LIKE, IT'S VERY OBVIOUS. IT'S LIKE, OKAY,
HE'S LIKE HE DOESN'T REALLY CARE. HE'S LIKE,
CHECKED OUT. HE'S JUST LIKE DISENGAGED. YEAH. YOU
GOTTA JUST LIKE BE ON TOP OF THEM
AND YOU GOTTA BE IN CONTROL. LIKE THE
ONLY REASON WHY ONE OF YOUR REPS WOULD
DO THAT IS BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT, YOU'RE LACKING
CONTROL AND YOU'RE LACKING CONFRONT INTERESTING. SO USUALLY
PEOPLE THINK IT'S SWITCHED, THE MORE THE REP
MAKES THE MORE YOU CAN LAY OFF OF
THEM. YEAH. IT'S IT'S LIKE WALKING THROUGH THAT
LIKE WHY IS THAT WHY DO YOU NEED
TO STAY ON TOP OF THEM? BECAUSE THEY
THINK, ONCE THEY START MAKING MONEY, THEY'RE IN
THIS NEW REALM.
AND THEY'RE LIKE, WOW LIKE IT'S NICE BUT
WHAT THEY DON'T REALIZE IS THEY'RE STILL COMPLETELY
BROKE.
LIKE THEY HAVE NO MONEY.
EVEN IF THEY'RE MAKING 40 50, 60 K
A MONTH. THERE ARE, THEY'RE BROKE.
AND THEY HAVE TO UNDERSTAND THAT THEY'RE AT
THE SAME LEVEL AS THEY WERE WHEN THEY
WHEN THEY CAME IN. THERE ARE SO MANY
DIFFERENT LEVELS. THEY HAVE TO DO THE SAME
AMOUNT OF CHANGE THAT THEY HAD TO CHANGE
WHEN THEY STARTED AT THAT POINT OF 100
OR YOU KNOW WHATEVER TWO THREE, FOUR HUNDRED
K A YEAR. THEY HAVE TO CHANGE THAT
MUCH AGAIN TO GET TO THE
FOUR. FIVE, SIX A MILLION DOLLARS A YEAR.
SO THEY JUST HAVE YOU JUST IT JUST
ALL COMES DOWN TO COMMUNICATION AND CONFRONT, LIKE
YOU HAVE TO BE IN COMMUNICATION WITH YOUR
TOP REPS. MMM. AND YOU HAVE TO YOU
SAY MORE THAN YOUR MORE THAN THE BOTTOM
REP, 100%, THE