when I was 11 years old,
My biochemistry teacher, he gave me this book
hero that was called the illusion of paradise.
And there he would.
Describe the biological and chemical processes.
That happen in your body. Once you consume
this to that substance, it was mainly related
to
illegal drugs, but alcohol was one of this
addictive substances that he covered
so it turns out that when you drink
alcohol, the thing that happens is that
Your brain cells.
Become paralyzed.
They become literally zombies. And then next day,
Sometime after the party is over.
Some of your brain cells die and never
get to normal.
so think about us, if your brain is
this most valuable tool you have in your
journey to success
And happiness.
Why would you destroy this tool?
For short-term pleasure.
This sounds ridiculous. Yeah, in many ways, it's
a poison that in our body but by
way of advice, what advice would you give
to people who consider not drinking? You know,
a lot of people use alcohol
To enable them to have a vibrant social
life.
There's a lot of pressures from society.
You know, at a party to drink. So
you can socialize
What advice would you give to them?
To people who imagine having a social life
without alcohol.
Well, first of all, don't be afraid to
be contrarian, set your own rules.
Secondly if you feel you need to drink,
they must be some problem. You're trying to
conceal. There's something that some Theory or not
ready to
confront.
And you have to address this fear.
If there is a good-looking girl, you're afraid
to approach.
Get rid of this fear. Approached her practice,
do it again and again, it's pretty banal.
But this advice Works fix the underlying problem,
which is usually at the very bottom is
always going to be fear work on that.
And very often people are trying to escape
something in their lives with alcohol. What is
it? They're trying to escape. What is this
problem?
You have to get to the bottom of
it.
Your mind is trying to tell you something
valuable.
And instead of addressing a directly you are,
flooding, it in alcohol.
Which is sort of a spiritual painkiller.
But works only temporarily and then you have
to pay the debt with interest.